{
    "id": "1c58a28ef80b4922bf11f336a880fd82",
    "title": "Question words exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "9ad24047b87b47ebba6cd22c68c8777d",
            "title": "Questions Words Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "………………… I love weekends!",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "How",
                        "How do"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "How ………………… grown!",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "you have",
                        "have you"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Hold it in both hands ……………….. Mummy does.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "as",
                        "like",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………. do you know?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "How",
                        "Why",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… do you call this?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "What",
                        "Why"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………… do you think about her new boyfriend?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "What",
                        "How"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………. about eating out this evening?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "What",
                        "How",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………… a beautiful painting!",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "What",
                        "How"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… marvelous!",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "What",
                        "How",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… do you weigh?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "How",
                        "How much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}